Class of 1924 Records, 1920-1989
Smith College Archives
Class of 1924 Records
1920-1989
Smith College. Class of 1924.
RG 80 UUID:ed18f371-06c4-4d7f-aff5-ac61152b015f
27 boxes (21.5 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1924.
The Class of 1924 was the forty-sixth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1924 Records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1924, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1924 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Commencement 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 1)
- Commencement Music 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 2)
- Commencement Photographs 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 3)
- Freshman Frolic 1920 (Box 1963, Folder 4)
- Freshman Handbook 1920-1921 (Box 1963, Folder 5)
- Groups 1920-1924 (Box 1963, Folder 6)
- History 1924, undated (Box 1963, Folder 7)
- Hoop Rolling 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 8)
- Ivy Day 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day-Photographs 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 10)
- Last Chapel 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 11)
- Last Sing 1924 (Box 1963, Folder 12)
- Class Letters 1934-1989 (Box 1963, Folder 13)
- Photographs 1923-1924 (Box 1963, Folder 14)
- Reunions 1927-1929 (Box 1963, Folder 15)
- Reunions 1934 (Box 1963, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1939-1944 (Box 1963, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1949 (Box 1963, Folder 18)
- Reunions-Correspondence 1949 (Box 1963, Folder 19)
- Reunions-Notebook 1949 (Box 1963, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1954 (Box 1963, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1959 (Box 1963, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1964 (Box 1963.1, Folder 1)
- Reunions-Letters to Reunion Chairmen 1964 (Box 1963.1, Folder 2)
- Reunions-Notebook 1964-1969 (Box 1963.1, Folder 3)
- Reunions 1969 (Box 1963.1, Folder 4)
- Reunions 1974 (Box 1963.1, Folder 5)
- Reunions 1979 (Box 1963.1, Folder 6)
- Reunions 1984 (Box 1963.1, Folder 7)
- Senior Dramatics 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 8)
- Senior Dramatics 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 9)
- Songs undated (Box 1963.1, Folder 10)
- Class Supper 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 11)
- Sophomore Carnival 1922 (Box 1963.1, Folder 12)
- Step Sings 1924 (Box 1963.1, Folder 13)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Class Secretary's Card Files (Box OV)
- Reunion Scrapbook and Class Scrapbook 1949, 1922-1924 (Box OV)
- Reunion Scrapbooks 1954-1969 (Box OV)